here's a convenient and safe way for you
to change your name Sun Life policies Mo
first log to your sunlife pH mobile app
then tap on service request icon at the
bottom select send account related
requests and fourth enter the OTP sent
to your registered philippin mobile
number
[Music]
n OTP fifth click request for name
change and select the policies to be
updated then download the name change
request form and fill it out then upload
the form together with your supporting
documents as needed birth certificate or
marriage certificate
ifame click summary and then click
submit tracking number I guy at isend
through email and SMS that's it for the
name change request tune in for more
videos thank you